《老爸们》在摄影棚现场录制
Dads is recorded in front of a live studio audience.
嘿  呃  你知道哪有好吃的泰国菜么?
Hey, u uh, do you know any good place to get Thai food?
我刚才说"你能推荐个好吃的泰国饭馆么?"
I said, "Can you recommend a good Thai restaurant?"
你是在问我
And you're asking me.
是啊  很明显
Yeah. Obviously.
为什么问我?
Why me?
因为你有个表哥叫Wai Mi
[Wai Mi:与Why me同音  Wai是What An Idiot缩写  意为"真是个白痴"]
Because you have a cousin named Wai Mi.
Warner  Eli变成种族主义者了
Warner, Eli's being racist.
Eli  不许这样
Eli, stop being racist.
但是Veronica不给我推荐泰国饭馆
But Veronica won't give me Thai restaurant recommendations.
Veronica  给Eli推荐一家泰国饭馆
Veronica, give Eli Thai restaurant recommendations.
可我不吃泰国菜啊
But I don't eat Thai.
所有东西尝起来都像是辣味宠物
Everything tastes like spicy pets.
现在你才是种族主义者
Now you're being racist.
要是你拿自己的种族开玩笑  就不是种族主义者了
You're not racist if you're making fun of your own race.
嘿  嘿  咱们把种族主义者
Hey, hey. Let's just leave what's racist
留给白人媒体讨论吧  好么?
up to the white media, okay?
老爸们  第一季  第十集
天天美剧字幕组 www.ttmeiju.com
本字幕仅供学习交流 严禁用于商业用途
翻译: 水果虫虫  败家玩意  RobRach  米亚十三
校对: 兰陵笑笑生
老爸  这个护发素我昨天才买的
Dad, I just bought this conditioner yesterday.
今天你怎么就全都用光了?
How did you already use it all?
不要问连你自己都不想知道答案的问题
Don't ask questions you don't want to hear the answer to.
你把所有麦片都吃了?
Did you eat the last of the cereal?
还有所有的鸡蛋?
And the last of the eggs?
洗澡的时候我流失了很多蛋白质嘛
I lost a lot of protein in the shower.
你灌了这么多咖啡怎么还能整天打呼噜?
How you drink so much coffee then snore all day?
我不打呼噜
I don't snore.
是么?  你打呼噜
Si? You snore.
抬起你那大肥脑袋
You tilt your big fat head back,
张开你那张大肥嘴
open big fat mouth
呼噜声就像犹太大肥驴一样
and make sound like big fat Jewish donkey.
你整天都在煲电话粥
You're on the phone all day,
五五二十五  上山打老虎
yakkata bappita, cinco de cinco.
你到底在聊什么?
What do you even talk about?
"我在吸尘  你在干什么?"
"I'm vacuuming. What are you doing?"
"吸尘"
"Vacuuming."
你在添油加醋
You make that up.
这是最严重的一次交火
This is the worst episode of Crossfire ever.
听着  老爸  从现在开始
Listen, Dad, from now on,
未经我的同意不许再吃我的食物
no more eating my food without my permission.
你在干什么?
What are you doing?
哦  你想要什么的话  下来我办公室
Oh, if you want something, you can just come down to my office
找我申请吧
and ask for it.
不许锁住冰箱
You can't lock the fridge.
我要吃饭才能活下去
I need food to live.
我知道
I know.
这时间可不太好
This not a good time.
吸尘
Vacuuming.
老爸  起床了!
Dad, wake up!
你就要把自己点着了  Crawford
You almost set yourself on fire, Crawford.
哦  别管那个了
Well, never mind that.
我刚才正梦到价值百万的创意
I just dreamed a million dollar idea.
- 真的?  - 是啊
- Really? - Yeah.
我们那么多人的父母都去世了是吧?
You know how so many of our parents are dead?
哦  要赚钱了
Oh, cha-ching.
好吧  要是有人提供一种服务  你可以提出要求
Okay, what if there was a service where you could call
然后有两个人依稀看上去长得像你过世的父母一样
and have two people who look vaguely like your dead parents
过来做客一起聚聚  这主意怎么样?
come over and hang out?
光是想象一下  呃  就让人激动不已了
Just imagine, uh, the thrill o-of playing catch
找一个  一个陌生人  只要你把眼镜摘了
with a-a stranger who, if you take your glasses off,
他就能当你爸爸
could be your dad.
他会来我家然后躺在沙发里
Would he come and fall asleep on the couch with a lit cigar
像你一样嘴里叼着点燃的雪茄就睡着了么?
in his mouth like you just did?
抱歉啦  护林熊
[Smokey the Bear:美国护林提示漫画形象]
I'm sorry, Smokey the Bear.
只有这样我才有绝佳创意
That's how I do my best thinking.
好吧  要是雪茄把沙发点着了
Okay, what if the cigar caught the couch on fire
然后火焰把威士忌都毁了呢?
and the flames hit the scotch?
我是谁啊  科学家么?
What am I, a scientist?
好的  要是你再叼着雪茄睡着
Okay. If you fall asleep just one more time
哪怕一次  我就亲自拿喷雾杀虫剂
with a lit cigar in your mouth, I will take bug spray
还有打火机把你点着  行么?
and a lighter and I will set you on fire myself. Okay?
我肯定会这么干的
I'm gonna do it.
听上去你可能很快就需要去市场
Well, it sounds like you might soon be in the market
买个山寨老爸了
for a look-alike dad.
老爸  这上面只有"生意"二字
Dad, this just says "Business."
是啊  是棋盘游戏里的
Yeah. It's from a board game.
其他的上面是"寻欢作乐"和"滚床单"
The others say "Pleasure" And "Sex."
那是Edna专门给我做的玉米卷饼
Those are the carnitas that Edna made special for me.
你要是不愿意什么东西被吃掉  就别放进冰箱里
You don't want something eaten, don't leave it in the fridge.
但是...  怎么...
But... how...
- 你是怎么...  - 我打不开的冰箱
- how did you... - They haven't made the refrigerator
他们还没发明出来呢
I can't break food out of.
顺便说一下
By the way,
我把冰格填满了
I refilled the ice tray.
不用客气
You're welcome.
老爸  有一条干净毛巾
Dad, there was a clean towel in here
早晨我放在那的
when I left this morning.
你是说这条?
You mean this one?
抱歉  我留着洗澡用了
Sorry, I'm saving it for my shower.
不  不行  我给过你很多毛巾了
No, no. I gave you towels.
我的被你用过之后  毛巾都卷成一团
Whenever you use mine, they wind up looking
就像一战时期医院里用过的一样
like they're from a World War I hospital.
我都不知道上面那种颜色的体液是什么东西
I don't even know what bodily fluids are those colors.
是我脚趾头上流出来的黑血
It's the black blood from my toes.
你六年前就该知道了
You should be getting that in about six years.
把毛巾还给我  老爸  那是我的
Give me the towel, Dad. It's mine.
我只用了一面  剩下的地方归你用了
I'll only use one side. The rest is all yours.
两面都是我的
Both sides are mine.
把毛巾给我
Give me the towel.
Edna  阻止他进入浴室!
Edna! Stop him before he gets to the bathroom!
收到  老大!
Copy that, boss!
我可不想干掉你  Edna  但是我会下手的
I don't want to kill you, Edna, but I will.
Edna视死如归
Edna laughs at death.
干得好  Edna  谢谢
Nice work, Edna. Thank you.
把毛巾给我  老爸
Give me the towel, Dad.
- 不  不  不  - 把那条毛巾给我  老爸
- No. No. No. - You give me that towel, Dad.
给我毛巾
Give me the towel.
好吧
Fine!
哦  我的头
Ooh, my head!
老爸  你还好么?
Dad, are you okay?
哦  他需要毛巾
Ooh. He need towel.
难以置信  急救室竟然
I can't believe the emergency room
先收治其他人然后才轮到我
took all those other people before me.
老爸  有辆缆车翻了
Dad, a cable car tipped over.
都是缺胳膊断腿的  你只是缝了两针
People lost limbs. You got two stitches.
可是我先挂号的
Still, I signed in first.
嘿  我收到了你的短信  嘿
Hey, I got your text. Hey.
David  你感觉怎么样
David, how are you feeling?
我只想说"你给我止痛药然后闭嘴"
I feel like "Shut up and give me my painkillers."
得啦  得啦  天哪
Here, here. My goodness.
给你  David  用这个服药
Here, David, wash it down with this.
不不不  爸爸
No, no, no. No, no, Dad.
你不该喝酒的  好吧
You're not supposed to drink alcohol with... Okay.
我现在发现
Now, I find if you do everything
当你偏不按着处方来
the prescription label says not to,
一切都更加奏效
it works better.
反向而行  事半功倍
Double the "Don't"s, triple the buzz.
你是Eli Sachs吗
Eli Sachs?
是的
Yes.
我是美国特勤局Silverton警官
I'm Special Officer Silverton.
移民局的来了!
Immigration!
请进吧
Won't you please come in?
呃  我很抱歉  Silverton警官
Um, I'm sorry, Officer Silverton.
这儿有点混乱
It's just a little chaotic.
我爸爸撞到了头  在急诊室观察了一晚上
My dad bumped his head; we spent the night in the E.R.
我知道
I know.
当有老人受伤的案件时
When there's an injury involving an elderly parent,
我们会主动上门调查
we're automatically sent to investigate.
女士
Ma'am.
你会很吃惊的发现
You'd be surprised how many children
有不少人会对自己的父母
are driven to commit acts of violence
使用暴力
against their elderly parents.
什么  你觉得是我干的?
What? You think that I did this?
哦  天哪  相信我
Oh, my gosh, believe me,
我如果想伤害我爸爸  他连头都不会有了
if I had wanted to hurt my dad, he wouldn't even have a head.
对吧  就像这样
Am I right? Like...
我很高兴我没有提醒你
Well, I'm glad I didn't mention
你所说的一切都将作为呈堂证供
that anything you say can be used against you.
因为你刚才说的话将会作为呈堂证供
Because now I'm going to use that against you.
你不会找到比Eli更孝顺的儿子了
You're not going to find a more caring son than Eli.
谢谢你  朋友
Thank you, buddy.
- 很感谢你  - 没事
- I appreciate that. - Yeah.
谁锁上了冰箱
Who chained the refrigerator shut?
Eli  但是  呃
Eli, but, uh,
事实上
in his defense,
他爸爸把他的蛋吃光了所以他
his dad ate all of his eggs and he was...
要砍掉他爸爸的头
Going to cut his head off?
是的  不是
Yeah. No.
我永远都不会那么做
No, I would never do that.
爸爸  和他讲道理
Dad, tell him.
这威士忌的确和我的止痛药
Man, that whisky pushed
相辅相成
my painkillers into high gear.
你竟然让你的父亲同时服用麻醉药和酒精
You allowed your father to take narcotics with alcohol?
噢  得啦  这有什么关系
Oh, come on, what's the big deal?
我儿子一直就这么干的
My son does that all the time.
他说我不清醒时省事得多
He says it's easier to have me unconscious and out of his hair.
这是胡说八道
That's crazy.
我可喜欢你来烦我了
I love you in my hair.
是啊  我希望他老婆也这样
Yeah, I wish his wife did.
她想用驱虫剂做一个火焰喷射器
She wants to make a flamethrower
让后把我点着
out of bug spray and set me on fire.
那可是对人身安全的威胁
Okay, that's a threat of bodily harm.
我要依法把你们转移
By law, I have to remove you from the premises.
什么  我们被捕了吗
What, like, we're under arrest?
不  我需要转移你们的父亲
No, I need to remove your fathers
重新安置到安全的地方
and relocate them to a safe place.
等等  那么我们可以呆在这儿喽?
Wait, so-so we-we get to stay here?
事实上  我才不管你们干嘛
Uh, actually, I don't care what you do.
我的工作可不是
My job description
替人渣策划派对
is not "Scumbag party planner".
我们会有新的身份吗
Will we get new identities?
我一直想改名成"Nick"
I've always wanted to be "Nick".
- 他说了那地方很安全  - 如果不得不这样的话
- Well, if he says it's safe. - Well, if you have to.
- 要遵守法律  - 对啊
- I mean, laws are laws. - Yeah.
- 那就把他们领走吧  - 对
- Take them away. - Yes.
- 这终于发生了吗  - 噢
- Did that just actually happen? - I mean...
噢  天哪
Oh, my God!
我们庆祝一下吧
Let's hang out, man,
- 是呀  - 看场电影或者干点什么别的
- Yeah. - watch a movie or something.
Edna  你干嘛要躲起来
Edna, why are you hiding?
Eli
我有可能是非法移民的
there is a chance I may not be legal.
啊  多大的可能
Ooo-What kind of chance?
百分之百
100%.
你们真是疯了
This is crazy.
就这样让他把你们的爸爸带走了?
You just let them take your dads away?
不不不  我们做了所有能做的
No, no, no, we did everything we could.
我们说了"嘿"
We said "Hey"...
和类似的话
...and stuff like that.
你都不知道他把他们带去哪了
You don't even know where they took them.
当然知道  带走了
Sure we do, away.
是啊  所以别说我们不在乎
Yeah, so don't tell us we don't care.
Warner  他是你爸爸
Warner, he's your father.
哦  别对我来这套
Oh, don't get all "He's your father" on me.
你还威胁要放火烧了他呢
You're the one who threatened to set him on fire.
这都能判重罪了
You pushed this into felony territory.
这无关乎谁对谁错  好吗
This isn't about whose fault it is, okay?
我们都知道这是谁的错
We all know whose fault it is.
就这一次不用听我爸念叨
It's about just once not hearing my dad's theory
Sully Sullenberger故意迫降了飞机
[Sully Sullenberger:著名机长 飞机被飞鸟撞击后成功迫降]
that Sully Sullenberger crashed his plane on purpose.
对呀  或者听我爸宣称肯尼迪
Yeah, or my dad's theory that John F. Kennedy
死于自杀
actually committed suicide.
我只是  我真不能明白
I just... I don't understand
你们俩怎么还能安心坐在这里而不去找爸爸
how you guys are not out looking for your dads.
我们的猫只走丢了半小时
I mean, our cat was missing for half an hour
你就翻遍了整个镇
and you were all over town looking for it.
亲爱的  Bootsy就像家人一样
Honey, Bootsy was like family.
等等
Wait a minute.
Boosty是走丢的?
Bootsy ran away?
但你告诉我
But you told me that she went to live
她去和一位贵妇人住在城堡里了
with a rich lady in a castle.
没事的 Eli
It's okay, Eli.
别碰我
Don't touch me.
噢  天哪
Oh, my gosh.
没有老爸的早晨真美好
What a beautiful dad-free morning.
噢  真是太美妙了
Oh, it was so nice
不用五点半被
not to wake up at 5:30 a.m.
I Love Lucy吵醒
[I Love Lucy: 上个世纪60年代风靡美国的一部热播电视剧]
with a blast of I Love Lucy,
还得听某人嚷嚷
followed by someone yelling,
"女人可真乏味"
"Women aren't funny!"
回到家不用发现一个68岁的老人
It's so great not coming home to a 68-year-old man
卡在狗门里真是太棒了
stuck in your doggy door.
等等  你们的爸爸走了可你们却不在乎
Wait... so your dads are just gone and you guys don't care?
噢  不不不
Oh, no, no, no, no.
我们会弄清楚的
We'll clear all this up
两个礼拜后肯定把他们弄回来
and get 'em back in a couple of weeks,
或者在我们填完这个一页的表格之后  谁知道多长时间呢
or however long it takes to fill out the one-page form.
对  没错
Right, yeah.
好吧  别等太长时间了
Well, don't wait too long.
老年护理中心各种不靠谱
Elder foster care is crazy.
我之前看过一个新闻
I saw this thing on the news
上面说给老年人下药然后给他们吃狗食
where they drugged them and fed them dog food.
嘿  电视上有些狗食看起来蛮好吃的
Hey, some of that dog food on TV looks pretty good.
比如说里面有真正大块牛腩的那个
Like that one with the real chunks of sirloin.
我知道这是比一般狗粮贵点
I mean, I know it costs more than regular dog food,
但是值了
but I'm worth it.
"老年护理中心虐待老人"
"Elderly foster care abuse."
我的天啊
Oh, my God...
等下  来看看这些照片
Wait, look at these pictures.
哇  她说的是真的诶
Wow, she's right.
好恶心
Oh, gross.
不对  这老太太不是笑着呢么
Oh, no, this lady's got a smile on her face.
等下  那不是她的脸
Wait, that's not her face.
我的天啊
Oh, my God.
啊  要是  那些虐待狂们
Hey, what if... some sadistic monster
正在折磨我们的老爸怎么办?
is torturing our dads right now?
欢迎来到我们快乐的大家庭
So welcome to our happy home
我是本  我是琼安
I am Ben And I am Joan
你的孩子们把你打得鼻青脸肿
Your children beat you black and blue
不管是用书还是鞋
With a book or with a shoe
我们知道了
We get it! Yeah.
知道了  你们是好人呗
We get it, you're nice people.
欢迎回家
Welcome home.
棒极了
This is great.
我在家要是被拥抱
The only time I get hugged at home
只有在他们帮我把疝气推回去的时候
is when they're pushing my hernia back in.
只要女士就好
Just the woman.
诶  唐尼和玛丽  厕所在哪呢?
Hey, Donny and Marie, where's the bathroom?
哦  嘘嘘的地方在这呢
Oh! Tinkle Center is right over here.
这可是皇家冲冲3000
That's the Royal Flush 3000.
你可真有眼光  先生
Well, you've got quite the fecal eye, mister.
这东西能冲下去一整块法国面包
You could put a loaf of French bread down that thing
然后冲到海里以后完全不变形
and find it bobbing in the ocean, not even bent.
介意我试用一下不?
Mind if I take her for a spin?
哦  当然不  只要你还坐在上面的时候别冲就行
Oh, sure. Just-just don't flush it while you're still on it.
它会直接把你的心带走的
It'll suck your heart out.
他已经虏获了我得心了
It already has.
你知道  我曾经犯过一个错
You know, I once made the mistake
就是告诉了一个会说话的鹦鹉
of telling a talking parrot
我得信用卡号
my credit card number.
损失了八千刀然后上了两次庭之后
$8,000 and two court cases later,
我对动物王国重新肃然起敬
I have a newfound respect for the animal kingdom.
是吧
Yeah.
你知道  动物直觉上是要来取悦我们的
You know, animals instinctively want to entertain us.
这就是为什么熊喜欢边骑自行车
That's why bears love riding bicycles
边被鞭打着
while being whipped.
你太搞笑了
Well, you're a hoot.
是的  你们真的超搞笑
Yeah... you guys sure are,
我得告诉你们
and I gotta tell you,
"搞笑"可是我们给出的最高赞美了
"hoot" is the highest compliment we give.
真真的
It's true.
我这一辈子就只见过三个特搞笑的人
I've only met three hoots in my entire life,
而我面前就有两个
and I'm looking at two of 'em.
呃  不好意思  你们的杯垫在哪呢?
Well, uh, excuse me, where are your, uh, coasters?
杯垫?
Coasters?
你真是傻的可爱啊  先生
You are an enormous silly goose, mister.
你把你的杯子想放哪就放哪就行
You just put your drink wherever you want.
真的?
Really?
看到没  我们喜欢在我们的家具上留下水渍
See, we like having rings on our furniture.
看到他们就想起那些善良的老人
It reminds us of all the nice older people
我们非常荣幸照顾过他们
we've had the privilege of sheltering.
这是加斯留下的
This was Gus.
他女儿用铲雪锹打了他的头
His daughter hit him over the head with a snow shovel.
他各种憎恨圣诞节
He sure hated Christmas.
好了  这是厄尔留下的
All right, this is Earl.
厄尔的女儿对他实施了水刑
Earl's daughter water-boarded him.
太恐怖了
That's horrible.
他们其实得到了一些挺有用的信息
Well, they actually got some pretty useful information.
好吧  加州怪名字的小镇还真多
All right, California has so many weird town names.
就是的
I know!
"看那黑鬼"
"Vista del Negro."
他们应该不能用这个名吧?
Can they even have that sign?
还有多远啊?
How much further away is it?
这个手机定位软件说还有五英里
The, uh, the Find-A-Phone app says five miles.
我忘不了刚看的那些虐待老人的照片
I-I can't get some of those abuse images out of my head.
呃  是不?
Ugh, right?
- 尤其是那张有…  - 对
- Especially that one with the, uh…  - Yeah.
或者是那几张有…
Or-or the ones with, uh...
哦  天啊  别再提醒我了
Oh, God, don't remind me.
还有那个有…
How about that one with...
我没看到那一张
No, I didn't see that one.
最好不要有人把我们老爸缝到一起去
Nobody better be sewing our dads together
然后做成一个人体蜈蚣
to make a human centipede.
其实得要三个人才能组成一个人体蜈蚣
Actually, you need three to make a human centipede.
哦  对哦  我好无知好尴尬啊
Oh, you're right. I'm so embarrassed.
我以后再也不跟我老爸吵架了
Well, I am never gonna fight with my dad again.
他甚至在我嘿咻的时候出现
He can even walk in on me having sex
我都不会骂他让他离开了
and I'm not gonna yell at him to leave.
真的?
Really?
你愿意让你老爸观看你嘿咻?
You're going to let your dad watch you having sex?
他从来没来过我少年联赛的比赛
Well, he never came to my Little League games.
这差不多么
It's kind of the same thing.
还真不一样
Not really.
好吧  重点是
Well, the point is,
我们以后要做最有爱最有耐心的儿子
we are going to be the most loving and tolerant sons ever.
同意
Hear, hear.
我们永远都做不到那样
We're never gonna be like that.
确实
No, no.
但是我们说出了这个话
But even us just talking about it
就代表我们是最完美的儿子
makes us the most awesome sons ever.
- 同意  - 好的
- Hear, hear.  - Yeah.
不对不对  这里转出去
No, no, no, no. Turn off here, here.
- 《洛奇》  - 《黑天鹅》
- Rocky. - Black Swan.
- 《洛奇2》  - 《爵士春秋》
- Rocky 2. - All That Jazz.
- 《洛奇3》  - 《浑身是劲》
- Rocky 3. - Footloose!
啊  《基督最后的诱惑》
Uh, The Last Temptation of Christ.
《冰上圆舞曲》
Ice Castles!
- 对啦  《冰上圆舞曲》  - 太牛了
- Yes, Ice Castles! - Yes!
- 太棒了  真厉害  - 你答对了 真棒
- Yes, yes! - Oh, you got it! Yes!
你真棒了  不  你才是最棒
You're so good. No, you're the good one.
- 是的  - 你最棒
- Good. - You're the good one!
- 我知道  - 你最棒
- I know. - You're the good one.
好了  David  该你了
All right, David, you are up.
David!
加油  David  加油
Come on, David, come on.
- 加油  - 来了
- Come on. - Here we go.
没问题
All right.
-《阿波罗13号》  - 天啊
- Apollo 13. - No.
好吧  再说一遍  你不应该
Okay. Again, you're not supposed to just
直接把名字说出来  可是你
say the title out loud, but you...
好吧  我还是要给你一分
You know, I'm gonna give you a point anyway,
因为这次你没直接把纸条扔火里
'cause this time, you didn't just throw it into the fire.
我能说啥  我玩得太爽了
What can I say? I'm having fun.
够了  你们两个变态  离我们老爸远点
All right, you sickos, get away from our dads!
Warner  快去看看他们是不是被缝一起了
Warner, check to see they haven't been sewn together.
呃  我  我从这儿就能看到没被缝一起
Oh, I can... I can kind of see that they haven't.
David  Crawford  站我身后
David, Crawford, stand behind me.
我会保护你们的
I will protect you
就像正义的卫生棉一样
like a panty shield of righteousness.
我在我的防狼口哨里放了颗新鲜豆子
And I have put a a fresh pea in my rape whistle,
所以我向你保证
so it'll be good and loud,
它吹起来又大又响
I guarantee you that.
- 没事  让我们来  - 对
- It's okay. We got this. - Yeah.
你来这儿干什么  Eli
What are you doing here, Eli?
老爸  听我说
Dad, listen...
我很抱歉我们之前吵架了
I'm sorry that we fought before.
你比我大多数毛巾重要多了
You mean more to me than most of my towels.
老爸
And Dad,
对不起我冲你嚷嚷了
I'm sorry I yelled at you.
Camila和我只是担心
It's just, Camila and I worry so much
你会毁了我们家
that you're gonna destroy our home,
我们的生意  孩子  所以我们  呃
business, and children, that we, uh...
我们反应过度了
we-we overreact.
来吧  我们带你们离开这里
So come on, we're taking you guys out of here.
明早再跟社工说清楚
We'll sort it out with Social Services in the morning.
- 走吧  - 不了  多谢
- Let's go. - No, thanks.
你什么意思
What do you mean?
我们喜欢这儿
We like it here.
我们也不再是你们的负担了
And we are no longer a burden to you.
等等  不是吧
Wait... come on.
这跟你们的幸福无关
This isn't about your happiness.
这是为了让我们的良心不受谴责
This is about our guilty conscience.
所以  快走吧
So let's go.
他们还没认识他们的室友呢
They haven't even met their roommates.
他们可是对活宝
They're a couple of hoots.
现在你们有四个活宝了
Now you're up to four hoots
我不相信你了
and you've lost my trust.
等一下
Wait a minute.
什么室友
What roommates?
我俩
Us.
他们是什么东西
Who the hell are they?
我们老妈
Our mothers.
我要乡村绅士
I'll take Country Club,
你跟花花老爹
you take Bowling Alley.
他们一年前搬来的  说是"住几天"
They moved in a year ago for "Just a few days".
等一下
Wait a minute.
你们打算撮合我们的老爸和你们的老妈吗
You're trying to fix up our dads with your moms?
我们得让他们赶紧结婚
We need someone to marry them
- 这样他们才能搬出去  - 是啊
- to get them out of our house. - Yeah.
得了吧  我们走吧
Come on, let's get out of here.
嘿  别急嘛
Hey, not so fast.
我的秘密花园还等待浇灌呢
My secret garden needs tending.
快走  快走  快走  快走
Go! Go, go, go, go, go!
老爸  老爸  老爸
Dad, Dad, Dad.
你能别说了吗
You can stop saying that.
我们已经开出去半小时了
We've been driving for a half hour.
抱歉啊  只是我肾上腺素爆满
I'm sorry, I'm just so full of adrenaline.
我真不敢相信你竟然打了那个女人
Yeah, I can't believe you hit that woman.
我觉得我Sean Connery附身了
[Sean Connery: 第一任007扮演者]
I feel like Sean Connery.
我还是不确定那是个女人
I'm still not sure that was a woman.
打扰一下  我
Excuse me, I'm here...
等等  我还没读完这篇
Hang on, I'm not done with this story
"寻找真爱的Kelly Clarkson"
[Kelly Clarkson:美国当红流行女歌手]
about Kelly Clarkson finding true love.
哎呀  天啊
Oh, my God.
你怎么不早说你很帅啊
Why didn't you say you were hot?
我只是来检查一下你们的灭火器
I'm just here to inspect your fire extinguisher.
哦  我还是帮帮你吧
Oh, I better help you.
很难找的
It's really hard to find.
那不就是吗
There it is.
呃  啊  那个  可能是吧
Uh... yeah, that... that might be it.
你们消防员都好勇敢
All you guys are so brave.
我有个表哥就是"除黑人"镇的消防员
I-I have a cousin who's a fire fighter in Vista Del Negro.
啊  我很喜欢"除黑人"镇
Oh, well, I love Vista Del Negro.
我住在"尼私处"镇附近
I live one town over in Yorba Vulva.
我们凯旋啦
We're back!
从有恐怖老妈的好人手中
Operation: Rescue Dads
拯救老爸
From Nice People With Creepy Moms
任务圆满完成
was a huge success!
那你们很享受老爸回来的感觉吧
So you guys enjoying having your dads back?
可不是  邻居很想念我老爸
Yeah. And the neighbors missed
在门口取报纸时
my dad's robe blowing open
睡袍被风吹开的样子
when he gets the paper.
还有  我爸今天早上把厕所淹了
Yeah, my dad flooded the bathroom this morning
因为他打算把整条法式长面包冲下去
trying to flush a loaf of French bread down the toilet.
他一边抽一边叫
He just kept flushing and yelling,
"你可以的  你可以的"
"You can do it! You can do it!"
怎么回事
What's going on?
Eli先生  你爸不让我看我最爱的电视剧
Mr. Eli, your father won't let me watch my favorite show:
瓜达拉哈拉的真实主妇
[瓜达拉哈拉:墨西哥第二大城市]
The Real Housewives of Guadalajara.
我想看《国土安全》
I want to watch Homeland.
剧情老不变
Always same!
"我要疯了  我要疯了"
"I crazy, I crazy..."
砰啪
Ka-boom!
筒子们  我们现在是21世纪了
Guys, we live in the future.
可以把两部剧都录下来看
We can DVR both shows.
- 什么  - 什么
- What? - Que?
好了
Okay...
移民局
Inmagracion!
他们别想活捉Edna
They never take Edna alive!
欢迎加入天天美剧字幕组
@天天美剧
www.ttmeiju.com